Curriculum vitae

PERSONAL INFORMATION



MHD Fayez Al Habbal

- 💡 60m Street, near Royal Mall, Erbil, Iraq.
- Phone No. +9647512058316
- ✓ fayez.hb@hotmail.com

Date of birth 1 Jan 1993 | Nationality Syrian

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Experienced Customer Care Support Coordinator with a demonstrated history of working in the telecommunications industry. Skilled in Customer Service, Data Analysis, Reporting, Teamwork, Customer Satisfaction, Fast Typing and Microsoft Office. Strong support professional with a Master of Arts (MA) focused in Applied Linguistics from Damascus University.

WORK EXPERIENCE

1 Apr 2018- 30 Apr 2019

Quality Coordinator: Closed Loop Feedback (Day Shift) MTN Syria

Mezzeh, Damascus Syria

www.mtnsyr.com

- A closed-loop program is aimed at long-term improvements. Because of this customer-centric mind-set, a closed-loop program will seek to ultimately solve the internal issues that are causing customer problems in the first place. This isn't about tracking; it's about transformation.
- Depending on the NPS (Net Promoter Score) compared to the previous months, we locate some strong and weak points about the company's services, call centre and POS employees skills as well.

9 Jun 2015-31 Mar 2018

Customer Care: Contact Centre Representative (Night Shift)

MTN Syria

Mezzeh, Damascus (Syria)

www.mtnsyr.com

Curriculum vitae

- Dealing with a high range of personalities.
- Listen actively to customers' inquiries, understand their complaints, take their suggestions in consideration and inform them of the best offers and bundles that the company offers in return.
 - I have been chosen to give practical training for new employees.

EDUCATION

1 Jan 2016-1 Jan 2019

English Dept. MA in Applied Linguistics

Damascus University, Damascus (Syria)

- Thesis title: (The Effects of Digital Game-Based Learning on Developing EFL Learners' Vocabulary Skills). (Not Completed).
- The origins of English language and how to involve teachers and students in teaching and learning.
- A lot of sessions of how to teach English through new ways to smoothly deliver the information to students.
- Subjects: Principles of Teaching and Learning English Psychology in Teaching English Using Technology in Teaching English Discourse Analysis Education Management Evaluation and Measurement Management.

1 Oct 2010–14 May 2015

BA in English Literature

Damascus University, Damascus (Syria)

- Graduated: May 2015.
- Subjects studied: Poetry, Prose, Phonetics, Research Methodology, Composition, Comparative Literature, World Literature, American Literature
 - Graduated with a Good grade.

5 Sep 2009-10 Sep 2010

Syrian Baccalaureate, Literary Stream

Al-Andalos High School, Halbouni, Damascus (Syria)

- Subjects: Arabic, Cultural Studies, English language, French language, Philosophy, History, Geography.
 - Grade: Very Good.

LANGUAGES

- Arabic: Mother Tongue.
- English: Fluent.
- Turkish: Beginner Still learning.
- Kurdish (Sorani): Beginner Still learning.

Curriculum vitae

PERSONAL SKILLS

Communication skills

- Good Communication Skills.
- Active listener.
- Clarity and Concision.
- Easy Going & Flexible.
- Confidence.

Organizational/ managerial skills

- Problem Solving.
- Reliable.
- Collaborative.
- Candour.
- Team Player.

Digital competence

SELF-ASSESSMENT				
Information processing	Communication	Content creation	Safety	Problem solving
Proficient user	Basic user	Independent	Independent user	Proficient user

Digital competences - Self-assessment grid

Courses

- ICDL V.5
- Excellence in Customer Service.
- Ticketing (Amadeus System).

Online Courses

- "Write Professional Emails in English by Georgia Institute of Technology on Coursera. Certificate earned at Monday, April 1, 2019"
- "The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing by Google at Monday, August 26, 2019."
- "Adobe Photoshop Essentials by Lynda."